<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<kirtonj>
	<title>My Favourite Books</title>
	
	<student studentProgram="Computer Programmer" studentNumber="991355155">Jody Kirton</student>
	
	<mybooks>
		<book>
			<bookName bookImage="_images/eternityInTheirHearts.jpg" >Eternity in Their Hearts</bookName>
			<bookPlot bookType="Religion and Spirituality" >Has the God who prepared the gospel for all people groups also 
				prepared all people groups for the gospel? Don Richardson, author of the bestselling book Peace Child, 
				has studied cultures throughout the world and found startling evidence of belief in the one true God within 
				hundreds of them. In Eternity in Their Hearts, Richardson gives fascinating, real-life examples of ways 
				people groups have exhibited terms and concepts in their histories that have prepared them for the gospel.
			</bookPlot>
			<bookAuthor>Don Richardson</bookAuthor>
			<bookPublisher>Baker Publishing</bookPublisher>
			<bookPrice>$19.99</bookPrice>	
			<bookLink>https://www.chapters.indigo.ca/en-ca/books/eternity-in-their-hearts/9780764215582-item.html?ikwid</bookLink> 
			<bookRating>I give this book a rating of 4/5.  It's been years since I have read this book.  However of the many books
				I have read over the years, this one stands out to me.  I remember being able to relate to the story.  At a point 
				in time when I didn't know God, I was seeking to know Him, seeking to know the truth.  And when I seeked with a open 
				heart, I found Him.  Much like one of the characters in this book.
			</bookRating>
		</book>
		<book>
			<bookName bookImage="_images/iDaredToCallHimFather.jpg" >I Dared to Call Him Father</bookName>
			<bookPlot bookType="Biography and Memoir" >A first-person account of a wealthy Muslim woman in Pakistan who, 
				through a succession of supernatural events, came to know God as her Father.
			</bookPlot>
			<bookAuthor>Richard H. Schneider</bookAuthor>
			<bookPublisher>Baker Publishing</bookPublisher>
			<bookPrice>$15.73</bookPrice>	
			<bookLink>https://www.chapters.indigo.ca/en-ca/books/i-dared-to-call-him/9780800793241-item.html?ikwid</bookLink>
			<bookRating>I give this book a 4/5 rating.  I love how the main character in this books describes her life, how she is open
				and honest about her thoughts and feelings.  At times, this book has made me laugh out loud, and at times have made me cry. 
				A true and beautiful story about a life you will never forget. 
			</bookRating>			
		</book>
		<book>
			
			<bookName bookImage="_images/loveAndRespect.jpg" >Love and Respect</bookName>
			<bookPlot bookType="Family and Relationships" >A Marriage Book with a Difference! 
				A Message That Works.  Based on over three decades of counseling, 
				as well as scientific and biblical research, Dr. Emerson Eggerichs and his wife, Sarah, have already taken 
				the Love and Respectmessage across America and are changing the way couples talk to, think about, and treat 
				each other. What do you want for your marriage? Want some peace? Want to feel close? Want to feel valued? Want 
				to experience marriage the way God intended? Then why not try some Love and Respect.
			</bookPlot>
			<bookAuthor>Dr. Emerson Eggerichs</bookAuthor>
			<bookPublisher>Thomas Nelson</bookPublisher>
			<bookPrice>$19.99</bookPrice>	
			<bookLink>https://www.chapters.indigo.ca/en-ca/books/love-and-respect-the-love/9781591452461-item.html?ikwid</bookLink>
			<bookRating>I give this book a 5/5 rating.  I had heard many good things about this book from others, and so decided to
				read it for myself.  I really enjoyed how the foundation of this book is bibical.  Throughout my read, I had learned 
				better how to see things through my husbands eyes.  That in turn helped me to communicate better with him, and to 
				understand him better.  I have always had respect for my husband, and this book have helped me to show my husband that 
				I respect him in ways that he will see and understand more.
				</bookRating>			
		</book>
		<book>
			<bookName bookImage="_images/30LifePrinciples.jpg" >30 Life Principles</bookName>
			<bookPlot bookType="Religion and Spirituality" >Charles Stanley lays out 30 Life Principles that can help you 
				become more like Christ every day. This is accomplished through the power of His Holy Spirit, and through 
				your own diligence and discipline. 
				In this book, author Charles Stanley lays out 30 Life Principles that 
				can help you in the process. You will learn: "God's Word is an immovable anchor in times of storm," "fight 
				all your battles on your knees and you will win every time," "God acts on behalf of those who wait for Him," 
				and much more. These principles are laid out as a study guide for use in individual devotional or group 
				study-enough for every day of the month. 
				By practicing these 30 Life Principles, you will be cooperating 
				fully with the Spirit of God, and your life will grow into the likeness of Christ.
			</bookPlot>
			<bookAuthor>Charles F. Stanley</bookAuthor>
			<bookPublisher>Thomas Nelson</bookPublisher>
			<bookPrice>$12.50</bookPrice>		
			<bookLink>https://www.chapters.indigo.ca/en-ca/books/30-life-principles/9781418531089-item.html?ikwid</bookLink>
			<bookRating>I give this book a 5/5 rating.  This is actually a workbook that will take you though different books
				in the Bible, while providing encouraging commentary.  I really enjoyed studying my Bible with the help of this
				book.  The teachings are bibically sound, and the life examples given are very real and honest.  This is a book
				I can see myself going back to time and time again.
			</bookRating>
		</book>
	</mybooks>
</kirtonj>